http://www.getaboutoz.com/privacy

Please upgrade your broswer to view this website.
Click here to go to Microsoft Website
CLOSE
Leave your details and we'll be in touch within a day.
Thank you & welcome!
welovecampers
Got a Quote?
Click Here
Sign In
Email
Password
Remember me?
Can't access your account?
Media
Sign InForgot your password?
Privacy Policy
This document explains how we collect, use and disclose your personal information in connection with our car rental services. In this document when we use the term "we" or "us" it is a reference to We Love Car Rentals Pty Ltd Australian Company Number (ACN) 135 646 089. We may amend this policy from time to time, to make sure that it is accurate and up to date.
How do we collect your personal information?
1.1.  Generally, the only personal information we collect about you is that which you choose to tell us, or the personal information which we obtain from others.
1.2.  We may also collect information from a friend or someone who refers our services to you, or through your use of our website.
What personal information do we collect?
2.1.  We collect personal information which we consider relevant in providing and promoting our services to you, and operating our website.
2.2.  The type of information we collect includes, your name, address, telephone number, your computer's IP address and information provided at the time of booking and information provided from within your "My Account" section.
How do we use the information we collect?
3.1.  We use your personal information to provide and promote services to you.
3.2.  We may also use your personal information to maintain and develop our business systems including other websites we operate, to provide customer service, for traffic analysis, for billing purposes and to comply with the law.
3.3.  If you do not provide us with all or part of the personal information we require, it may prevent us from carrying out the things we have stated in clause
3.4.  If you receive promotional material you may choose to "opt out" of receiving this information.
3.5  We use your personal information for booking reminders
Do we disclose your personal information?
4.1.  We will not sell your personal information without your consent, unless we sell our business.
4.2.  We may choose to disclose your personal information to our contractors, our agents, our suppliers, government authorities and any other party who may assist us in providing services to you, or in promoting or marketing our services to you, or any party who purchases or seeks to purchase our business (or any part of it including a website).
4.3.  We may disclose your personal information to our contractors and suppliers who may be located outside of Australia where we do we will do so in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).
How do we use cookies?
5.1.  We use cookies to track your internet browsers behaviour, and also to store your favourite settings on our website.
5.2.  A cookie is a small file we store on your computer which holds the information we outlined in clause
5.3.  Every time you visit our site we can view this information.
How do we safeguard your personal information?
6.1.  We store your information in electronic form.
6.2.  We take all reasonable precautions to protect these records from misuse or unauthorised access by using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards.
6.3.  It is our practice to destroy, delete or de-identify your personal information when it is no longer needed.
How can you access information and ensure its accuracy?
7.1.  When you provide us with personal information (or other third parties) provide us with personal information, we assume that it is correct unless you tell us otherwise.
7.2.  Unless we know that personal information is incorrect, we cannot correct it. You can assist us, by telling us when the information we hold has changed and is no longer accurate.
7.3.  If you wish to access the personal information we hold about you, you can do so by making a request to us using the contact us form.
We welcome any questions or comments and invite you to contact us.
Getabout Oz - Campervan, Motorhome, Car and 4WD hire in Australia and New Zealand.
Contact us now for great deals from the best range of rental vehicles Australia and New Zealand wide.
Free call: 1300 613 833 | International: +61 2 9528 8015 | sales@getaboutoz.comResources | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | Rental Vehicle Excess Cover (Australia) | Rental Vehicle Excess Cover (NZ)
Getabout Oz Campervan, Motorhome, Car and 4WD hire in Australia and New Zealand.
Free call: 1300 613 833International: +61 2 9528 8015sales@getaboutoz.com© 2020 Getabout Oz | Terms | Privacy Policy | Rental Vehicle Excess Cover (Australia) | Rental Vehicle Excess Cover (NZ)
Service delivery is subject to our Payment Terms.
